Rinkham,
where on earth are you?
You're awake, Lady?
Luang Wisanu will surely give up everything to get his daughter back.
Rinkham.
Kaew.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I got here too late.
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault for being stubborn. I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
I'm getting you out of here.
Kaew, look out!
Kaew!
Are you awake?
Rinkham, how are you?
I am fine.
You're awake, huh?
A bodyguard like this, who could he possibly protect, right?
Don't get involved with her.
In that state, you still dare to order us around?
Still better than you lot, ganging up like dogs.
You've got a big mouth.
You're about to learn how you should really speak.
Bullying someone weaker like this shows you have no honor.
Honor?
Honor doesn't make me full.
But dishonorable people like you usually end up miserable.
You talk too much.
Rinkham, go!
Stay right here.
Wait here first.
I'll go deal with them.
No.
Let me protect you for once.
But it's dangerous.
Listen to me.
I will handle this myself.
Hey! What the heck?
A woman?
What kind of crazy bodyguard is a woman?
But that’s fine, makes it easier to handle.
We should be safe here for now.
You should rest.
Can I ask you something?
What is the truth?
Why... Why did you have to disguise yourself to join the military selection?
My real name is Kaewket.
My dad is sick.
So I disguised myself to enlist,
just to get the money to cure him.
I never thought I would get this close to you.
Or feel this way about you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that everything started with a lie.
I shouldn't have let it come to this.
I will go tell your dad.
And after this, we might never see each other again.